bangkokair.com 2018-11-14

# Privacy Policy - Bangkok Airways

* * *

#### Introduction

Bangkok Airways Public Company Limited (“We” or “PG”) is determined to safeguard your privacy by following the guidelines for protecting personal data collected from visiting our website, accessing our mobile application, or requesting our service. The Privacy Policy also covers all relevant data linked to us from a third-party.

#### Collection of Personal Data

  1. We collect your personal data only when you give us your data, or request for service through our website, mobile application, or any other channels; for examples, flight reservation, check-in, frequent flyer program application, newsletter application, special assistance request, including any offline transactions such as information provision through the ticket counters.
  2. We could also receive your personal information through a third-party, such as airline partners, business partners, travel agents or our service providers, tourism representatives, and relevant government officials.

#### Types of Personal Data

Types of personal data are varied depending on the collection situation and type of service you request. Your personal data will be used to make both online and offline transaction or requested service complete. This personal data, collected directly from you or from a third-party, are as follows;

  * Identification data such as name, photograph, sex, date of birth, passport number, citizen ID, or any ID numbers relating to personal identification.
  * Contact information such as address, telephone number, and email.
  * Payment information such as invoice information, credit or debit card information, and bank account information.
  * Travel information such as flight number, personal data of your travel companion, flight seat request, in-flight meal request, hotel request, and any supplementary service request.
  * Information from your marketing activity participation such as your registration details.
  * Statistics such as passenger number, travel statistics, and your access to our website.
  * Information from your access to our website such as IP Address, Cookies, Online Reservation System.

We do not collect and make use of any sensitive data such as race, religious belief, health information, criminal information, unless otherwise required by regulations and law or with your consent.

#### Usage of Personal Data

We may use your personal data for the following objectives;

  * Sourcing service or delivering our service.
  * Flight reservation, ticket sales, check-in, on-ground and in-flight service.
  * Coordinating and passing on data to airline partners in order to facilitate intercity flight connection.
  * Passenger identification and luggage claims.
  * Flight notification message or our offered assistance.
  * Facilitating and introducing various benefit programs for the members of the frequent flyer program.
  * Marketing, sales promotions and customer relations objectives such as communication on promotions, product and service from us and the business partners alike.
  * Making communication channels available for Q&A or response on complaints such as complaints on luggage claims or any losses.
  * Customer satisfaction survey, marketing research, and statistics analysis for required data to improve and innovate product and service.
  * Accountant or financial objectives such as credit card payment verification, billing and verification, refunding.
  * Security including in-flight safety.
  * Following the airport regulations.
  * Immigration and Customs procedures.
  * Abiding by the law, requirements, regulations, or any requests from the government officials such as compliance with subpoenas or judicial order or any other lawful requests.
  * Other objectives that support the abovementioned objectives or obtain your consent occasionally.

#### Disclosure of Personal Data

We may disclose or transfer your personal data to a third-party, inside or outside the Kingdom of Thailand. That will be done in accordance with proper and necessary measures, or regulation and law for the objectives indicated as in the followings;

  * Airline partners, business partners and alliances.
  * Affiliated companies, representatives, service providers, or business partners who service us or carry out any matters on behalf of us or responding to the customer's needs.
  * Banks and payment service providers such as credit or debit card companies.
  * Airport personnel.
  * Security and safety officers.
  * Immigration and Customs.
  * Government offices, regulators, and other relevant offices as permitted or stipulated in the law.

#### Links to Third-Party’s Websites

Website and mobile application may have links to the website of a third-party. If you follow these links, the Privacy Policy will not apply. Please be informed that we are unable to be responsible for any usage of your personal data by a third-party because this is considered beyond our reach of control. Please ensure that the Privacy Policy of each website that collects your personal data is favorable to you.

#### Securing Personal Data and Safety

  1. Your personal data is secured for as long as the objectives explained in this Privacy Policy is concerned, or under the rule of law, or for any legal actions.
  2. We will deploy technical measures and appropriate management to secure and safeguard your personal data such as the safety protocol (Secure Sockets Layer: SSL) for the Internet encryption.

#### Access or Correction of Personal Data

You can request an access or update and correct your personal data including all other rights enforced by the data privacy law; for instance, request of a copy of your personal data or request to suspend the usage or disclosure of your personal information if it’s been exploited beyond the abovementioned objectives or without your consent. The request for an access to your personal data or data correction must be done in written and is to be submitted together with a copy of your identification such as the flight reservation and your contact details. The documents must be mailed to the following address.

The Company’s Secretary Department  
Bangkok Airways Public Company Limited, 19th Floor  
99 Mu 14 Vibhavadirangsit Road, Chom Phon, Chatuchak, Bangkok 10900 Thailand.

#### Change of Privacy Policy

We may revise and change this Privacy Policy occasionally to be in line with any alterations of our service and operation. Your suggestions and opinions including the relevant law by the latest policy version will be announced on our website at www.bangkokair.com for you to understand the guidelines that we follow to safeguard your personal data.

If you have any questions, comments, or complaints about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [dataprivacy@bangkokair.com](mailto:dataprivacy@bangkokair.com)

This Privacy Policy is effective on May 25th, 2018.
